scoresandodds.com 2015-05-17

# Free sports betting trends and statistical analysis at ScoresAndOdds.com

  Page last updated on Sat May 16 21:12:15 EDT 2015

ScoresAndOdds.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.ScoresAndOdds.com 

## TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED

We collect aggregate information site-wide, including anonymous site statistics (e.g.: The number of page views or visits a certain section of our web site will receive). This information is used to improve the user experience and analyze the effectiveness of our advertising. This information is not stored in any way that would identify the actions or personal information of a specific user. 

During optional registration, we may ask you to provide us with two types of information: (1) personal information, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally, such as your name, e-mail address, and physical address; and (2) demographic information, such as gender, zip code, or similar information. We may collect this information at various places and forms on ScoresAndOdds.com, including registration forms for newsletters and other e-mail communications, when you communicate or otherwise interact with us, contests or sweepstakes or surveys. You may also be asked to choose a user name and password in order to identify yourself during future visits to the ScoresAndOdds.com. Do not use your real name or the name of any other actual person as your user name. Providing us with information about yourself is your choice, and you can always choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of ScoresAndOdds.com�s features. User information is not sold or shared with any other entities. 

## HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED

**Cookies**

ScoresAndOdds.com uses standard technology called "cookies," which are small text files that are transferred to your computer when you visit ScoresAndOdds.com if you allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your web browser to ScoresAndOdds.com whenever you visit ScoresAndOdds.com, and may make navigating and using ScoresAndOdds.com easier for you. Also, by tracking how and when you use ScoresAndOdds.com, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to ScoresAndOdds.com are based on data obtained from cookies. Additionally, accepting cookies may allow you to, among other things, personalize your experience on ScoresAndOdds.com. Cookies may also allow ScoresAndOdds.com to present to you advertising that may be of interest to you as well as limit how often you see certain ads that may detract from your user experience on ScoresAndOdds.com. If you do not want to allow information to be collected through the use of cookies, you can generally opt out of providing this information by setting your browser to reject cookies. However, please be aware that some areas of the ScoresAndOdds.com may not be able to provide complete functionality if you do not enable cookies. 

**Web Beacons**

ScoresAndOdds.com pages may contain electronic images (generally, single-pixel ".gif" images) called "web beacons." These web beacons allow us to monitor and collect certain anonymous information about the viewer of the web page, such as the type of browser being used, the IP address of the computer that the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed. ScoresAndOdds.com uses web beacons for purposes that include, without limitation, the following: 

  * Counting unique users (actually, unique web browsers), visits and page views. 
  * Monitoring traffic and conversion patterns through our various product and service offerings on ScoresAndOdds.com. 
  * Personalizing your experience when you visit ScoresAndOdds.com, including the advertising and content you see. 
  * Determining whether or not e-mail messages were opened, links were clicked or notifications/offers were acted upon. 

## CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS

ScoresAndOdds.com may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. 

## CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

ScoresAndOdds.com contains web pages through which you can change your e-mail subscriptions or correct or update the personal information you have provided to us through registration. 

## SECURITY

ScoresAndOdds.com incorporates reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that ScoresAndOdds.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to ScoresAndOdds.com via its Web Sites, and you do so at your own risk. 

## WITH WHOM INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED

The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others: 

Third parties providing services on our behalf 
    We employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf; examples include hosting or operating Web Sites, fulfilling orders for products and services purchased through the Web Sites, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, data analysis, marketing assistance, credit card payment processing, and customer service. These third parties may have access to your personal information for the purpose of performing such functions on the Web Sites' behalf and are bound by the terms of this privacy policy.
Non-Personal Information 
    We may share non-personal information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and web site usage information with third parties.
Business Transfers 
    In the event that ScoresAndOdds.com is sold or other similar transactions occur, the user database, including your personal information, may be one of the key business assets for the transaction. Hence, ScoresAndOdds.com reserves the right to disclose and transfer user information, including personal information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our assets, or other corporate change.

## CONSENT TO TRANSFER

The Web Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Web Sites or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer. 

## LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

This site contains links to other sites. ScoresAndOdds.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

By using the Web Sites, you acknowledge your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Company may update this Privacy Policy.
